Bug Log（with some metaphysics methods）

==============CP1===============


Bug : Page Fault 
Description: Page fault happens when we access to some memory. Paging initialization error
Who fix: Shihao Su
How fix: In page_initialization function(), initialize all memory we will use


Bug : IDT Error 
Description: Wrong interrupt occur when we try to have a special interrupt
Who fix: Ke Liu
How fix: The index of the IDT table doesn't meet with the requirement of Intel, so we rebuild the index.


==============CP2===============


Bug : Terminal Driver
Description: after typing enter, the cursor will appear in random place.
Who fix: Sicong Yu
How fix: store the position of the cursor, calculate the position where cursor should appear after typing enter


Bug: Backspace
Description: Backspace can't remove the characters from the input buffer
Who fix: Sicong Yu
How fix: Count the length of input buffer and replace with " " at that place


Bug: File System
Description: can't get correct content in one special file
Who fix: Shihao Su && Ke Liu
How fix: re-read the document and calculate the correct inode index and reading bytes


Bug: File System
Description: find the file when the length of the name of the file is lager than 32 bytes, but actually we shouldn't find it 
Who fix: Shihao Su && Ke Liu
How fix: Change the logic of the code for comparing the input name which we want to find and the file name stored in our file system. 


Bug: RTC initialization
Description: RTC is initializing abnormally
Who fix: Tianyi Meng
How fix: Fixed the values  


==============CP3===============


Bug: System call 
Description: general protection fault when we try to run system call of read and write 
Who fix: Ke Liu
How fix: Change the Descriptor Privilege Level(DPL) of the system call in IDT initialization


Bug: System call
Description: the corresponding read/write/open/close of the terminal/RTC/file/directory do not work
Who fix: Ke Liu 
How fix: build a function pointer structure 


Bug: Execute
Description: Can't go to user space as expected
Who fix: Sicong Yu && Shihao Su
How fix: Keep tracing our code by GDB and adjust the location of IRET 


Bug： Halt
Description： page fault when we enter exit
Who fix： Sicong Yu && Shihao Su
How fix：Keep tracing the stack by GDB and update the esp, eip when needed

==============CP4===============

Bug: Video map
Description: fish can't move as expected 
Who fix: Tianyi Meng 
How fix: change the value the input pointer points to rather than the pointer itself


==============CP5===============


Bug: Video 
Description: When we switch terminals, there is something left in the video
Who fix: Sicong Yu && Shihao Su
How fix: change 2 visual memory regions to 4 visual memory regions


Bug: Terminal switch
Description: page fault when we try to switch terminals
Who fix: Ke Liu && Tianyi Meng
How fix: initialize the memory where we used to store the content of different terminals video memory


Bug: Scheduler
Description: Run programs in one terminals and then switch to another terminals, there may be some bugs about page fault, general protection fault.
Who fix: Shihao Su && Sicong Yu
How fix: Delete some useless sti and cli.




